In recent years, the trend of
seeking insurance solutions that offer
protection has been increasing sharply, especially
as healthcare costs continue to rise.  The Willis Towers Watson
Global Healthcare Trends 2025 report
forecasts that healthcare costs
in Vietnam will increase by 11.2%, higher than the
global average of 10.4%.  In light of
this reality, Cru Maximum Protection was created to
support customers in building
optimal financial plans, while
increasing opportunities for accumulation towards
long-term goals through
flexible and customizable solutions.  Not only does Pudential comply
with the law and prioritize customer interests
, but its products
are also designed to optimize
protection per dollar of premium paid.  Always
committed to being a role model in the
insurance industry, we continue to affirm our
customer-centric approach in all our activities,
developing practical, flexible,
and tailored solutions to maximize protection. (I
'm currently working on this part.)